Register of the Institute of Economic Affairs (Great Britain) records
Hoover Institution Archives
- John B. Wood File, 1971-1989
  - Day files (Box 395)
    - 1975
      - September-December (Folder 4)
    - 1976
      - January-March (Folder 5)
      - April-May (Box 398, Folder 1)
      - June-October (Folder 2)
      - November-December (Folder 3)
    - 1977
      - January-March (Folder 4)
      - April-June (Folder 5)
      - July-September (Box 399, Folder 1)
      - October-December (Folder 2)
    - 1978
      - January-April (Folder 3)
      - May-August (Folder 4)
      - September-December (Folder 5)
    - 1979 (Box 400)
      - January-April (Folder 1)
      - May-August (Folder 2)
      - September-December (Folder 3)
    - 1980
      - January-April (Folder 4)
      - May-August (Folder 5)
      - September-December (Folder 6)
    - [January-September missing], 1981 October-December (Box 401, Folder 1)
    - [1982 August-1985 December missing], 1982 January-July (Folder 2)
    - 1986
      - January-June (Folder 3)
      - July-December (Folder 4)
    - [January-April missing], 1987 May-December (Folder 5)
    - 1988
      - January-April (Folder 6)
      - May-August (Folder 7)
      - September-December (Box 402, Folder 1)
    - 1989 January-September (Folder 2)
  - Memoranda (Folder 3)
  - Publishing projects
    - Manser, William Arthur Peete, Britain in Balance, Correspondence with readers J. H. Dunning, J. K. Horsefield, G. Hutton, F. W. Paish, and E. V. Morgan, 1971 (Folder 4)
    - Sawers, David, Competition in the Air: What Europe Can Learn from the USA, 1987
      - Background material re airfare. Two papers by Nicholas Bethell and two brochures (Folder 5)
      - Correspondence
        - With author, Includes note by R. Harris [?], 1986 February - 1987 March (Folder 6)
        - With readers John Hibbs, Peter S. Masefield, and Stephen Wheatcroft (Folder 7)
      - Typescripts
        - General
          - Version No. 1, chapters 1-5 (Folder 8)
          - Version No. 2, chapters 1-5 (Folder 9)
        - Preface by J. B. Wood (Box 403, Folder 1)
      - Galleys (incomplete) (Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous. Revised pages, "Summary and Conclusions," "European Air Transport," and notes by J. B. Wood (Folder 3)
  - Subject file
    - Aims of Industry. See also Correspondence/Alternative Bookshop (Folder 4)
    - Association of British Chambers of Commerce
      - 1979-1983 August (Folder 5)
      - 1983 September-December (Folder 6)
      - 1984 (Folder 7)
      - 1985-1988 (Folder 8)
    - M. Forsyth Associates. Andrew Veitch, "Tory MPs' privatisation links condemned," Guardian, [?], 1987 July 5 (Folder 9)
    - Nationalized Industries Policy Group. Includes correspondence with Ralph Harris and David Alexander (Selsdon Group), papers, briefs, brochures, and memoranda (Folder 10)
  - Writings
    - Introduction to Victoria Curzon Price's book Europe's Last Chance, 1988 (Folder 11)
- Photographs, 1971-1989
  1 print depicting Harold Wincott, undated, and 8 prints depicting recipients of the Wincott Foundation press awards (annual awards for financial journalism), 1971-1989. See also Incremental Materials.
  - 1 print depicting Harold Wincott, undated (Box 404, Folder 1)
  - 2 prints and 2 contact sheets depicting recipients of the Wincott Foundation press awards (annual awards for financial journalism), 1971 (Folder 2)
  - 6 prints depicting recipients of the Wincott Foundation press awards (annual awards for financial journalism), 1989 (Folder 3)
- Incremental Materials, 1947-2010
  Scope and contents note
  Arranged in 20 subseries, the Incremental Materials include correspondence, memoranda, meeting minutes, publications, manuscripts, press releases, conference programs and proceedings, clippings, notes, subject files, and financial records documenting the activities of IEA. The arrangement of the subseries mirrors the original accession.
  - Conference, Seminar, and Lecture File, 1989-2000
    Includes correspondence, proceedings, conference programs, publicity material, lecture transparencies, memoranda, drafts of lectures, and miscellany regarding events held by IEA or attended by IEA members. Many of the conferences hosted by others were attended by Colin Robinson of IEA. These files include his lecture notes and presentation materials. The series is arranged in three groups, General, Hosted by IEA, and Hosted by Others. Files arranged by date of conference.
    - General
      - Brochures, flyers, and pamphlets, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 405: 1-2)
      - Declined invitations, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 405: 3-4)
      - Exhibitions, displays, and sponsorship for conferences hosted by others, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 405: 5)
      - Proposed or cancelled events file
        - "British Universities: The Way Ahead,", 1993 (Box-folder 405: 6)
        - "The Future of Work,", 1989-1994 (Box-folder 405: 7)
        - National Teachers Conference, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 405: 8)
        - South Africa conference, 1993 (Box-folder 405: 9)
        - Unemployment conference, 1993 (Box-folder 405: 10)
    - Hosted by IEA
      - 1993 May. A Level Economics Seminar, IEA and Sheffield University (Box-folder 406: 1)
      - 1993 October. "The Future of International Regulation of Air Transport," (Box-folder 406: 2)
      - 1993 October-Novemeber. Lectures on Regulation, IEA and London Business School (Box-folder 406: 3-6)
      - 1994 April. Annual Energy Conference, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 406: 7)
      - 1994 September-October. Lectures on Regulation, IEA and London Business School, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 406: 8)
      - 1994 October. Edinburgh Economic Seminar (Box-folder 407: 1)
      - 1994 November. Second Annual International Aviation Conference (Box-folder 407: 2)
      - 1994 November. Second Annual Energy Conference (Box-folder 407: 3)
      - 1995 Monetary Conference, IEA and CATO, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 407: 4)
      - 1995 May. "The Cost of Medical Progress," Gordon Tullock, seminar, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 407: 5)
      - 1995 May. Pensions and Financial Services, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 407: 6)
      - 1995 June. Second Annual International Gas Conference, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 407: 7)
      - 1995 July. Second Annual Electricity Conference (Box-folder 407: 8)
      - 1995 October. Environmenal risk, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 407: 9)
      - 1995 October-December. Lectures on Regulation, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 407: 10)
      - 1995 October-December. Lectures on Regulation (cont'd.), 1994-1996 (Box-folder 408: 1)
      - 1995 October. "The Public and Utilities:What Has Gone Wrong?,", 1995-1996 (Box-folder 408: 2)
      - 1995 Novemeber. Seventh Annual International State of the Economy Conference (Box-folder 408: 3-4)
      - 1995 November. Annual European Energy Forum (Box-folder 408: 5)
      - 1995 December. Annual Air Transport Conference (Box-folder 408: 6)
      - 1996 May. Third Annual International Gas Conference (Box-folder 408: 7)
      - 1996 July. Third Annual Electricity Conference, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 408: 8)
      - 1996 October-November. Lectures on Regulation, IEA and London Business School (Box-folder 408: 9)
      - 1996 October-November. Lectures on Regulation, IEA and London Business School (cont'd.) (Box-folder 409: 1)
      - 1996 November. Eighth Annual International State of the Economy (Box-folder 409: 2)
      - 1996 November. European Energy Forum (Box-folder 409: 3)
      - 1996 November. European Monetary Union (Box-folder 409: 4)
      - 1997 February. "Allocating Airport Slots," Occassional Discussion, David Stackie, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 409: 5)
      - 1997 April. "Competition in Retailing: Market Boundaries and the MMC," (Box-folder 409: 6)
      - 1997 October-December. Lectures on Regulation, IEA and London Business School, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 409: 7-8)
      - 1997 October. State of the International Economy (Box-folder 409: 9-10)
      - 1997 November. "The Future of Water: Ending the Policy Drought,", 1997-1998 (Box-folder 410: 1-2)
      - 1997 November-December. Occasional Discucssion, "Financial Regulation" and "Strategic Defence Review," (Box-folder 410: 3)
      - 1998 June. Fifth Annual Gas Conference, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 410: 4)
      - 1998 June. State of the British Economy (Box-folder 410: 5)
      - 1998 October-December. Lectures on Regulation, IEA and London Business School (Box-folder 410: 6-7)
      - 1998 November. International State of the Economy (Box-folder 410: 8)
      - 1998 November. International State of the Economy (cont'd.) (Box-folder 411: 1)
    - Hosted by Others
      - 1993 April. British Institue of Energy Economics, rountable (Box-folder 411: 2)
      - 1993 October. Institution of Eletronics and Electrical Incorporated Engineers (Box-folder 411: 3)
      - 1994 July. "The National Energy and Power Management Conference for the NHS, Public and Private Sectors," (Box-folder 411: 4-5)
      - 1994 October. Institut Euro, "Public Services: Towards a New Model of Operation,", 1994-1995 (Box-folder 411: 6)
      - 1995 February. Scottish Nuclear, "Diversity and Security in Electricity Supply," workshop (Box-folder 411: 7)
      - 1995 February. University of Surrey, Nuclear review conference, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 411: 8)
      - 1995 March. Cato Institute and Institute for Energy, "New Horizons in Electric Power Deregulation,", 1994-1995 (Box-folder 411: 9)
      - 1995 April. British Institute of International and Comparative Law, lecture, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 411: 10)
      - 1995 June. Houe of Commons, Trade and Industry Committee (Box-folder 411: 11)
      - 1995 November. Hertford College, Regulatory Policy Research Centre Seminar Series, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 412: 1)
      - 1995 December. British instittue of Energy Economics, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 412: 2)
      - 1996 January. University of Portsmouth, public lecture, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 412: 3)
      - 1997 April-May. Adam Smith Society, "The Future of the Italian Electricity Market,", 1997-1998 (Box-folder 412: 4)
      - 1997 April-September. Adam Smith Institute, Taiwan Power Company conference (Box-folder 412: 5)
      - 1997 May. Instituto de Crédito Oficial, Madrid, Spain (Box-folder 412: 6)
      - 1997 May. Privatisation in Kuwait (Box-folder 412: 7)
      - 1997 August. Japan Public Choice Society, international conference (Box-folder 412: 8)
      - 1997 December. British Institute of Energy Economics, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 412: 9)
      - 1998 June. Adam Smith Society, "The Future of the Italian Teclecom Market," (Box-folder 412: 10)
      - 1998 December. ELBA corporation, Kuwait, privatization conference (Box-folder 412: 11)
  - Economic Affairs File, 1983-1998
    Includes manuscripts, correspondence, memoranda, proofs, and press releases relating to the journal published by IEA. Arranged in three subseries: Contributors, Journal Issues, and Subject File. Journal Issues arranged by issue number. Other subseries arranged alphabetically. See also Incremental Materials of 2014.
    - Contributors, 1992-1993
      - General, 1992, undated (Box-folder 413: 1)
      - A, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 413: 2)
      - Ba-Bl, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 413: 3)
      - Bo-Bu, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 413: 4)
      - C, 1993 (Box-folder 413: 5)
      - D, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 413: 6)
      - E, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 413: 7)
      - F, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 413: 8)
      - G, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 413: 9)
      - Ha-He, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 413: 10)
      - Hi-Hu, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 413: 11)
      - J, 1992 (Box-folder 413: 12)
      - K, 1993 (Box-folder 413: 13)
      - Mc, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 413: 14)
      - Ma-Ml, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 413: 15)
      - Mm-Mz, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 414: 1)
      - O, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 414: 2)
      - P, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 414: 3)
      - R, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 414: 4)
      - Sa-Sg, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 414: 5)
      - Sh-Sl, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 414: 6)
      - Sm-Sz, 1992 (Box-folder 414: 7)
      - T, 1992 (Box-folder 414: 8)
      - V, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 414: 9)
      - Wa-Wi, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 414: 10)
      - Wm-Wz, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 414: 11)
      - Y-Z, 1993 (Box-folder 414: 12)
    - Journal Issues
      - Volume 13, Issue 5
        - Book reviews, 1993 (Box-folder 414: 13)
        - Columns, 1993 (Box-folder 414: 14)
        - Comments and letters, 1993 (Box-folder 415: 1)
        - Main articles, 1993 (Box-folder 415: 2)
        - Symposium, "Morality of Markets,", 1993 (Box-folder 415: 3)
      - Volume 14, Issue 1
        - Book reviews, 1993 (Box-folder 415: 4)
        - Columns, 1993 (Box-folder 415: 5)
        - Comments and letters, 1993 (Box-folder 415: 6)
        - Main articles, 1993 (Box-folder 415: 7-8)
        - State of the Economy Conference, 1993 (Box-folder 415: 9)
      - Volume 14, Issue 2
        - Book reviews, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 415: 10)
        - Columns, 1994 (Box-folder 416: 1)
        - Comments, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 416: 2)
        - Main articles, 1994 (Box-folder 416: 3)
        - Symposium on transport policy, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 416: 4)
      - Volume 14, Issue 3
        - Book reviews, 1994 (Box-folder 416: 5)
        - Columns, 1994 (Box-folder 416: 6)
        - Comments and letters, 1994 (Box-folder 416: 7)
        - Conference on environmental economics, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 416: 8)
        - Main articles, 1994 (Box-folder 416: 9)
      - Volume 14, Issue 4
        - Book reviews, 1994 (Box-folder 416: 10)
        - Columns, 1994 (Box-folder 417: 1)
        - Comments and letters, 1994 (Box-folder 417: 2)
        - Conference, "Regulating Industry and Commerce,", 1994 (Box-folder 417: 3-4)
        - Main articles, 1994 (Box-folder 417: 5-6)
      - Volume 14, Issue 5
        - Book reviews, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 417: 7)
        - Columns, 1994 (Box-folder 417: 8)
        - Comments and letters, 1994 (Box-folder 417: 9)
        - Conference on social benefits, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 418: 1)
        - Main articles, 1994 (Box-folder 418: 2-3)
      - Volume 15, Issue 1
        - Book reviews, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 418: 4)
        - Columns, 1994 (Box-folder 418: 5)
        - Comments and letters, 1994 (Box-folder 418: 6)
        - Conference, State of the Economy, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 418: 7)
        - Main articles, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 418: 8)
        - Main articles (cont'd.), 1994-1995 (Box-folder 419: 1-2)
      - Volume 15, Issue 2
        - Book reviews, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 419: 3)
        - Columns, 1995 (Box-folder 419: 4)
        - Comments and letters, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 419: 5)
        - Main articles, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 419: 6)
      - Volume 15, Issue 3
        - Book reviews, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 419: 7)
        - Columns, 1995 (Box-folder 419: 8)
        - Comments, 1995 (Box-folder 419: 9)
        - General, 1995 (Box-folder 419: 10)
      - Volume 15, Issue 4
        - Book reviews, 1995 (Box-folder 420: 1)
        - Columns, 1995 (Box-folder 420: 2)
        - Comments, 1995 (Box-folder 420: 3)
        - Main articles, 1995 (Box-folder 420: 4)
        - Symposium on monetary policy, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 420: 5)
      - Volume 16, Issue 1
        - Book reviews, 1995 (Box-folder 420: 6)
        - Columns, 1995 (Box-folder 420: 7)
        - Comments, 1995 (Box-folder 420: 8)
        - Conference on environmental risk, 1995 (Box-folder 420: 9)
        - Main articles, 1995 (Box-folder 420: 10)
      - Volume 16, Issue 2
        - Book reviews, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 420: 11)
        - Columns, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 420: 12)
        - Short articles and review articles, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 420: 13)
        - Symposium, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 420: 14)
      - Volume 16, Issue 3
        - Book reviews, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 420: 15)
        - Short articles and review articles, 1996 (Box-folder 420: 16)
        - Columns, 1996 (Box-folder 420: 17)
        - Main articles, 1996 (Box-folder 421: 1)
        - Symposium on European monetary affairs, 1996 (Box-folder 421: 2)
      - Volume 16, Issue 4
        - Book reviews, 1996 (Box-folder 421: 3)
        - Columns, 1996 (Box-folder 421: 4)
        - Correspondence and memoranda, 1996 (Box-folder 421: 5)
        - Main articles, 1996 (Box-folder 421: 6)
        - Short articles, 1996 (Box-folder 421: 7)
      - Volume 16, Issue 5
        - Book reviews, 1996 (Box-folder 421: 8)
        - Columns, 1996 (Box-folder 421: 9)
        - Main articles, 1996 (Box-folder 421: 10)
        - Short articles, 1996 (Box-folder 421: 11)
      - Volume 17, Issue 1
        - Book reviews, 1997 (Box-folder 421: 12)
        - Columns, 1997 (Box-folder 421: 13)
        - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 421: 14)
        - Correspondence (cont'd.), 1996-1997 (Box-folder 422: 1)
        - Main articles, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 422: 2)
        - Short articles, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 422: 3)
      - Volume 17, Issue 2
        - Book reviews, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 422: 4)
        - Columns, 1997 (Box-folder 422: 5)
        - Correspondence and proofs, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 422: 6-7)
        - Main articles, 1996-1997, undated (Box-folder 422: 8)
        - Other articles, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 422: 9)
      - Volume 17, Issue 3
        - Book reviews, undated (Box-folder 423: 1)
        - Columns, 1997 (Box-folder 423: 2)
        - Correspondence and proofs, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 423: 3-4)
        - Main articles, 1997 (Box-folder 423: 5)
        - Other articles, 1997 (Box-folder 423: 6)
      - Volume 17, Issue 4
        - Correspondence, 1997 (Box-folder 423: 7)
        - Main articles, 1997 (Box-folder 423: 8-9)
      - Volume 18, Issue 1
        - Book reviews, 1998 (Box-folder 424: 1)
        - Columns, 1997 (Box-folder 424: 2)
        - Main articles, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 424: 3)
        - Other articles, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 424: 4)
        - Proofs and general, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 424: 5)
      - Volume 18, Issue 2
        - Book reviews, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 424: 6)
        - Columns, 1998 (Box-folder 424: 7)
        - Main articles, 1998 (Box-folder 424: 8)
        - Other articles, 1998, undated (Box-folder 424: 9)
        - Proofs and general, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 424: 10)
      - Volume 18, Issue 3
        - Book reviews, 1998 (Box-folder 425: 1)
        - Columns, undated (Box-folder 425: 2)
        - Main articles, 1998 (Box-folder 425: 3)
        - Other articles, 1998 (Box-folder 425: 4)
        - Proofs and general, 1998 (Box-folder 425: 5)
      - Volume 18, Issue 4
        - Book reviews, 1998 (Box-folder 425: 6)
        - Columns, 1998 (Box-folder 425: 7)
        - Main articles, undated (Box-folder 425: 8)
        - Other articles, 1998 (Box-folder 425: 9)
        - Proofs and general, 1998 (Box-folder 425: 10)
    - Subject File
      - Book reviews, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 425: 11)
      - Columnists, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 425: 12)
      - General, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 426: 1)
      - Miscellaneous, 1983-1996 (Box-folder 426: 2)
      - Production costs, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 426: 3)
      - Subscriptions, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 426: 4)
  - Financial Records, 1960-1997
    Includes accounts containing balance sheets and auditor reports.
    - Accounts
      - 1962 (Box-folder 426: 5)
      - 1963 (Box-folder 426: 6)
      - 1964 (Box-folder 426: 7)
      - 1965 (Box-folder 426: 8)
      - 1966 (Box-folder 426: 9)
      - 1967 (Box-folder 426: 10)
      - 1968 (Box-folder 426: 11)
      - 1969 (Box-folder 426: 12)
      - 1970 (Box-folder 426: 13)
      - 1972 (Box-folder 426: 14)
      - 1974 (Box-folder 426: 15)
      - 1975 (Box-folder 426: 16)
      - 1977 (Box-folder 426: 17)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 426: 18)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 426: 19)
      - 1980 (Box-folder 426: 20)
      - 1981 (Box-folder 426: 21)
      - 1982 (Box-folder 426: 22)
      - 1983 (Box-folder 426: 23)
      - 1984 (Box-folder 427: 1)
      - 1985 (Box-folder 427: 2-3)
      - 1986 (Box-folder 427: 4)
      - 1987 (Box-folder 427: 5)
      - 1988 (Box-folder 427: 6)
      - 1989 (Box-folder 427: 7)
      - 1990 (Box-folder 427: 8)
      - 1991 (Box-folder 427: 9)
      - 1992 (Box-folder 427: 10)
      - 1993 (Box-folder 427: 11)
      - 1994 (Box-folder 427: 12)
      - 1995 (Box-folder 427: 13)
      - 1996 (Box-folder 427: 14)
      - 1997 (Box-folder 427: 15)
    - Estimates, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 427: 16)
    - Tax documents, 1970-1971, 1979 (Box-folder 427: 17)
  - Meeting Materials, 1981-2009
    Includes minutes, agendas, reports on various departments of IEA, correspondence, and memoranda. Arranged alphabetically by type of meeting.
    - Advisory Council
      - Christmas lunch, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 428: 1)
      - Correspondence, 1984-1993 (Box-folder 428: 2-3)
      - Meetings
        - 1987 (Box-folder 428: 4-5)
        - 1988 (Box-folder 428: 6-7)
        - 1989 (Box-folder 428: 8-9)
        - 1990 (Box-folder 428: 10-11)
        - 1991 (Box-folder 428: 12-13)
        - 1992 (Box-folder 429: 1-2)
        - 1993 (Box-folder 429: 3)
        - 1994 (Box-folder 429: 4-5)
        - 1995 (Box-folder 429: 6-7)
    - Annual General Meeting
      - 1997 (Box-folder 429: 8)
    - Finance Committee Meetings
      - 1997 (Box-folder 429: 9)
      - 1998 (Box-folder 429: 10)
    - Trustees Meetings
      - 1992 (Box-folder 430: 1-3)
      - 1993 (Box-folder 430: 4-11)
      - 1994 (Box-folder 430: 12-14)
      - 1994 (cont'd.) (Box-folder 431: 1-5)
      - 1995 (Box-folder 431: 6-12)
      - 1996 (Box-folder 431: 13)
      - 1996 (cont'd.) (Box-folder 432: 1-3)
      - 1997 (Box-folder 432: 4-7)
      - 1997 (cont'd.) (Box-folder 433: 1-2)
      - 1998 (Box-folder 433: 3-7)
      - 1999 (Box-folder 433: 8-9)
      - 1999 (cont'd.) (Box-folder 434: 1-4)
      - 2000 (Box-folder 434: 5-7)
      - 2001 (Box-folder 434: 8)
      - 2009 (Box-folder 434: 9)
  - Press Cuttings, 1996-2005
    Press cuttings on economic topics, IEA activities, and IEA members. Includes articles written by IEA members. Arranged chronologically.
    - General
      - 1996 (Box-folder 435: 1-5)
      - 1997 (Box-folder 435: 6-10)
      - 1997 (cont'd.) (Box-folder 436: 1-7)
      - 1998 (Box-folder 436: 8-14)
      - 1998 (cont'd.) (Box-folder 437: 1-5)
      - 1999 (Box-folder 437: 6-12)
      - 2005 (Box-folder 437: 13)
    - Subject
      - IEA Environmental Unit, 1998 (Box-folder 437: 14)
  - Publications File, 1987-1999
    Includes correspondence, manuscripts, contracts, and notes related to monographs, serials, and papers published by IEA. Arranged alphabetically by format.
    - Flyers, Occassional Lectures, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 438: 1)
    - Manuscripts
      - General
        Mainly includes correspondence, notes, synoposes, and contracts related to manuscripts. Few folders contain drafts.
        - Unidentified typescript, circa 1993 (Box-folder 438: 2)
        - Allen, Walter (editor), 1990-1995 (Box-folder 438: 3-4)
        - Barnett, Richard, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 438: 5)
        - Baron, Tony and Robert McGarvey, 1991 (Box-folder 438: 6)
        - Beesley, Michael, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 438: 7)
        - Bishop, Bill (editor), 1991 (Box-folder 438: 8)
        - Blaug, Mark, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 438: 9)
        - Bourlet, Jim, 1993 (Box-folder 439: 1)
        - Bracewell-Milnes, J. Barry, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 439: 2-3)
        - Brittan, Samuel, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 439: 4)
        - Chown, John, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 439: 5)
        - Collie, David, 1994 (Box-folder 439: 6)
        - Coleman, David (editor), 1992 (Box-folder 439: 7)
        - Congdon, Tim, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 439: 8)
        - Crockett, Richard, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 440: 1)
        - Curwen, Peter, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 440: 2)
        - Darby, Michael, 1992 (Box-folder 440: 3)
        - Dnes, Antony, 1993 (Box-folder 440: 4)
        - Dolye, Joseph, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 440: 5)
        - Dunning, John and John Burton, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 440: 6)